ILR School Labor Economics Department Records /4307
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Labor Economics Department Records
2000-2014
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
Labor Economics Department
/4307
23 cubic feet
23 linear ft.
Records (documents).
8240101
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183> kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
Kheel Staff, March 09, 2015
EAD encoding:
Randall Miles, October 05, 2016
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations. Labor Economics Dept.
8240101
- Magnetic storage (Box 1)
  - Computer Tapes, 1971 (Box 1, Folder 1)
  - Computer Tapes Debbie Anderson/ Fran Blau, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 2)
  - Computer Tapes LUSTGART OTH445 Simone (Box 1, Folder 3)
  - Computer Tapes JANEA, 1977 (Box 1, Folder 4)
  - Computer Tapes LUSTGARTEN OTH445 Back-Up Tape of New SPSS File Fran (Box 1, Folder 5)
  - Computer Tapes Debbie Anderson/ Fran, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 6)
  - Computer Tapes (Box 1, Folder 7)
  - Computer Tapes MKIDX3, 1990 (Box 1, Folder 8)
  - Computer Tapes Diane W Fran SPSS System File Slot 1292 LUSTGARTEN (Box 1, Folder 9)
  - Computer Tapes GLORIA LOSTGART Slot #1010 (Box 1, Folder 10)
  - Computer Tapes U.S. Bureau of the Census U.S. Dept. of Commerce (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Magnetic storage (Box 2)
  - Information Paper 1986 Income Distribution Survey Australia (Previously: Income and Housing Survey) Sample File on Magnetic Tape (Box 2, Folder 1)
  - Docs. Related to Journal of Economic Behavior + Organizations and Econometrica, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 2)
  - Kahn + Murnighan, 1989 (Box 2, Folder 3)
  - JEBO Article + Practice Bargaining, 1991-1992 (Box 2, Folder 4)
  - NBA, 1988 (Box 2, Folder 5)
  - Merit Fall 1992 (Box 2, Folder 6)
  - Efficient Barg + Efficiency Wages, 1979-1990 (Box 2, Folder 7)
  - Docs. Related to Data Sets, 1978-1979 (Box 2, Folder 8)
  - Joint Hiring, 1979-1988 (Box 2, Folder 9)
  - Cola Variable Lists (Box 2, Folder 10)
  - Cola Project (Box 2, Folder 11)
  - Data Files For Spillover Project (Box 2, Folder 12)
  - Miscellaneous Variable USD, 1969 (Box 2, Folder 13)
  - Joint Hiring, 1986-1987 (Box 2, Folder 14)
  - Dodgers D0483 D0 BIN 15, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 15)
  - Dodgers D0483 D0 BIN 15, 1991 (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Reprints (Box 3)
  - The Effects of Race on Professional Football Players' Compensation, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 1)
  - Conjecture, uncertainty and cooperation in prisoner's dilemma games Some experimental evidence, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 2)
  - Discrimination in Professional Sports: A Survey of the Literature, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 3)
  - Cost-of-Living Clauses in Union Contracts: Determinants and Effects, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 4)
  - The Economic Journal (Folder 1 of 2), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 5)
  - The Economic Journal (Folder 2 of 2), 1991 (Box 3, Folder 6)
  - A General Experiment on Bargaining in Demand Games with Outside Options (Folder 1 of 7), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 7)
  - A General Experiment on Bargaining in Demand Games with Outside Options (Folder 2 of 7), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 8)
  - A General Experiment on Bargaining in Demand Games with Outside Options (Folder 3 of 7), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 9)
  - A General Experiment on Bargaining in Demand Games with Outside Options (Folder 4 of 7), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 10)
  - A General Experiment on Bargaining in Demand Games with Outside Options (Folder 5 of 7), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 11)
  - A General Experiment on Bargaining in Demand Games with Outside Options (Folder 6 of 7), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 12)
  - The Returns to Job Search: A Test of Two Models, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 13)
  - The Effect of Unions on the Earnings of Nonunion Workers, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 14)
  - The Demand For Labor Market Structure: An Economic Approach, 1984 (Box 3, Folder 15)
  - A General Experiment on Bargaining in Demand Games with Outside Options (Folder 7 of 7), 1993 (Box 3, Folder 16)
  - The Gender Earnings Gap: Learning from International Comparisons, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 17)
  - Unionism, Seniority, and Turnover, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 18)
  - Unions and Cooperative Behavior: The Effect of Discounting, 1993 (Box 3, Folder 19)
  - An Empirical Model of Employed Search, Unemployed Search, and Nonsearch, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 20)
  - Discussion (Box 3, Folder 21)
  - Customer Discrimination and Affirmative Action, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 22)
  - Journal of Economic Literature, Vol. XXIII (March 1985) (Box 3, Folder 23)
  - Journal of Economic Literature, Vol. XXIV (June 1986) (Box 3, Folder 24)
  - Research Frontiers in Industrial Relations and Human Resources 1992 (Box 3, Folder 25)
  - Racial Differences in Professional Basketball Players' Compensation, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 26)
  - The Impact of Wage Structure on Trends in U.S. Gender Wage Differentials: 1975-87, 1994 (Box 3, Folder 27)
  - Working Paper Series The Gender Earnings Gap: Some International Evidence, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 28)
  - Working Paper Series Race and Gender Pay Differentials, 1992 (Box 3, Folder 29)
  - The Impact of the Threat of Bankruptcy on the Structure of Compensation, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 30)
  - Customer Discrimination and Affirmative Action, 1991 (Box 3, Folder 31)
  - The Wage Impact of Job Search, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 32)
  - Inflation Uncertainty and Strike Activity, 1988 (Box 3, Folder 33)
  - Unions and the Employment Status of Nonunion Workers, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 34)
  - Union Strength and Wage Inflation, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 35)
  - Bargaining power, search theory and the Phillips curve, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 36)
  - The Determinants of Bargaining Structure In U.S. Manufacturing Industries, 1982 (Box 3, Folder 37)
  - Unions and Employment Stability: A Sequential Logit Approach, 1979 (Box 3, Folder 38)
  - Wage Indexation in the United States: Prospects for the 1980s (Box 3, Folder 39)
  - Unions and Internal Labor Markets: The Case of the San Francisco Longshoremen, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 40)
  - Wage Growth and Endogenous Experience, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 41)
  - The Demand for Labor Market Information, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 42)
  - Contingent Pay and Managerial Performance, 1990 (Box 3, Folder 43)
  - Bargaining Power, Search Theory and the Phillips Curve, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 44)
  - Union Spillover Effects on Unorganized Labor Markets, 1980 (Box 3, Folder 45)
  - On Estimating Discrimination in the Economy: Comment, 1985 (Box 3, Folder 46)
  - Unionism, Seniority, and Turnover, 1983 (Box 3, Folder 47)
  - A Model of Joint Wage and Hiring Discrimination, 1989 (Box 3, Folder 48)
- Reprints (Box 4)
  - Rising Wage Inequality and the U.S. Gender Gap (Folder 1 of 2), 1994 (Box 4, Folder 1)
  - Rising Wage Inequality and the U.S. Gender Gap (Folder 2 of 2), 1994 (Box 4, Folder 2)
  - Collective Bargaining and the Interindustry Wage Structure: International Evidence (Folder 1 of 4 ), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 3)
  - Collective Bargaining and the Interindustry Wage Structure: International Evidence (Folder 2 of 4 ), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 4)
  - Collective Bargaining and the Interindustry Wage Structure: International Evidence (Folder 3 of 4 ), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 5)
  - Collective Bargaining and the Interindustry Wage Structure: International Evidence (Folder 4 of 4 ), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 6)
  - The Gender Earnings Gap: Some International Evidence (Folder 1 of 3), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 7)
  - The Gender Earnings Gap: Some International Evidence (Folder 2 of 3), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 8)
  - The Gender Earnings Gap: Some International Evidence (Folder 3 of 3), 1995 (Box 4, Folder 9)
  - Against the Wind: Bargaining Recentralisation and Wage Inequality in Norway 1987-91, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 10)
  - Collective Bargaining and the Interindustry Wage Structure: International Evidence (Folder 5 of 6), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 11)
  - Collective Bargaining and the Interindustry Wage Structure: International Evidence (Folder 6 of 6), 1997 (Box 4, Folder 12)
  - International Differences in Male Wage Inequality: Institutions versus Market Forces, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 13)
  - International Differences in Male Wage Inequality: Institutions versus Market Forces, 1996 (Box 4, Folder 14)
  - Wage Structure and Gender Earnings Differentials: an International Comparison, 1995 (Box 4, Folder 15)
  - Swimming Upstream: Trends in the Gender Wage Differential in the 1980s, 1997 (Box 4, Folder 16)
  - International Differences in Male Wage Inequality: Institutions versus Market Forces (Folder 1 of 2), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 17)
  - International Differences in Male Wage Inequality: Institutions versus Market Forces (Folder 2 of 2), 1996 (Box 4, Folder 18)
  - The NBER Digest, 1993-1994 (Box 4, Folder 19)
  - Cost of Living Clauses in Union Contracts: Determinants and Effects, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 20)
  - Papers and Proceedings of the Hundred and Sixth Annual Meeting of the American Economic Association, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 21)
  - Nonunion Employment Regularity (Box 4, Folder 22)
  - Discrimination in Baseball, 1992 (Box 4, Folder 23)
  - Managerial Quality, Team Success, and Individual Player Performance in Major League Baseball, 1993 (Box 4, Folder 24)
  - Union Spillover Effects on Unorganized Labor Markets, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 25)
  - Docs. Related to Wages, 1981-1986 (Box 4, Folder 26)
  - Unemployment Insurance, Job Ques, and Systematic Job Search: An Equilibrium Approach, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 27)
  - Unions and Nonunion Wage Dispersion, 1987 (Box 4, Folder 28)
  - On Estimating Discrimination in the Economy: Comment, 1985 (Box 4, Folder 29)
  - An Empirical Model of Employed Search, Unemployed Search, and Nonsearch, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 30)
  - The Demand For Labor Market Structure: An Economic Approach, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 31)
  - Against the Wind: Bargaining Recentralisation and Wage Inequality in Norway 1987-91, 1998 (Box 4, Folder 32)
  - Rising Wage Inequality and the U.S. Gender Gap, 1994 (Box 4, Folder 33)
  - Union Impact: A Reduced Form Approach, 1977 (Box 4, Folder 34)
  - A General Experiment on Bargaining in Demand Games with Outside Options (Box 4, Folder 35)
  - Wage Growth and Endogenous Experience, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 36)
  - Unionism, Seniority, and Turnover, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 37)
  - Bargaining Power, Search Theory and the Phillips Curve, 1980 (Box 4, Folder 38)
  - Job Search and Unionized Employment, 1983 (Box 4, Folder 39)
  - The Relative Effects of Employed and Unemployed Job Search, 1982 (Box 4, Folder 40)
  - The Effect of Collective Bargaining on Production Technique: A Theoretical Analysis, 1984 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- Computer disks (Box 5)
  - 3 1/2 Inch Floppies (Box 5, Folder 1)
    Scope and Contents
    8 Floppy Disks
  - Zip Drives- 39 (Box 5, Folder 2)
  - Computer Tapes Borjas, George, 1988 (Box 5, Folder 3)
  - Computer Tapes (Box 5, Folder 4)
  - Computer Tapes FRANB2, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 5)
  - Computer Tapes FRANB1, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 6)
  - Computer Tapes CNS 703, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 7)
  - Computer Tapes X09350, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 8)
  - Computer Tapes Simone w/ Percent Female Lustgarten- Slot 1275 (Box 5, Folder 9)
  - Computer Tapes X09352, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 10)
  - Computer Tapes X09353, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 11)
  - Computer Tapes U.S. Bureau of The Census U.S. Dept. Of Commerce (Box 5, Folder 12)
  - Computer Tapes FranB3, 1990 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Computer disks (Box 6)
  - Computer Media (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Blau course files, ILR LE 340, 1997-1998 (Box 7)
  - Welfare + Poverty Article 1, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 1)
  - Welfare + Poverty Article 2 (Box 7, Folder 2)
  - Welfare + Poverty Article 3, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 3)
  - Welfare + Poverty Article 4, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 4)
  - Welfare + Poverty Article 5, 1992 (Box 7, Folder 5)
  - Health Care Article 3, 1991 (Box 7, Folder 6)
  - Health Care Article 4, 1981 (Box 7, Folder 7)
  - Health Care Optional Readings (Box 7, Folder 8)
  - Old Age Article 1, 1990 (Box 7, Folder 9)
  - Old Age Article 2 (Box 7, Folder 10)
  - Old Age Article 3 (Box 7, Folder 11)
  - Old Age Article 4, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 12)
  - Old Age Article 5 (Box 7, Folder 13)
  - Old Age Article 6 (Box 7, Folder 14)
  - Economic Security, 1993-1998 (Box 7, Folder 15)
  - Docs. Related to Journal of Economic Literature, 1986-1998 (Box 7, Folder 16)
  - ILRE 340 spring 98 Packet, 1998 (Box 7, Folder 17)
  - Spring 1997 Packet (Box 7, Folder 18)
  - Introduction Handouts, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 19)
  - Unemployment Insurance Handouts, 1994-1995 (Box 7, Folder 20)
  - The Problem of Old Age Handouts, 1995 (Box 7, Folder 21)
  - Disability Handouts, 1994 (Box 7, Folder 22)
  - Healthcare Handouts, 1997 (Box 7, Folder 23)
  - Welfare and Poverty Handouts, 1991-1996 (Box 7, Folder 24)
  - Conclusion Handouts, 1992-1995 (Box 7, Folder 25)
  - Introduction Article 1, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 26)
  - Introduction Article 2, 1985 (Box 7, Folder 27)
  - Introduction Article 3 (Box 7, Folder 28)
  - Introduction Article 4 (Box 7, Folder 29)
  - Introduction Article 5 (Box 7, Folder 30)
  - Disability Article 1, 1976-1996 (Box 7, Folder 31)
  - Introduction Article 6, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 32)
  - Disability Article 2, 1993 (Box 7, Folder 33)
  - Disability Article 3, 1988 (Box 7, Folder 34)
  - Health Care Article 1, 1986 (Box 7, Folder 35)
  - Health Care Article 2 (Box 7, Folder 36)
- Blau course files, ILR LE 340, 1997-1998 (Box 8)
  - Welfare Optional Readings, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 1)
  - Unemployment Insurance Article 1 (Box 8, Folder 2)
  - Unemployment Insurance Article 2, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 3)
  - Unemployment Insurance Article 3, 1989 (Box 8, Folder 4)
  - Unemployment Insurance Article 4, 1976 (Box 8, Folder 5)
  - "Risk and Responsibility" Chapter 6 Economic Report of the President, 1987 (Box 8, Folder 6)
  - "The Occupational Safety and Health Problem and " Alternative Policies for Regulating Industrial Safety" Chelius, J. (Box 8, Folder 7)
  - The Scientific Basis of Health and Safety Regulation R. Crandell + L. Lave Part Two Cotton Dust (Box 8, Folder 8)
  - NCCI Pamphlets (Box 8, Folder 9)
  - ILRE 340/541 Module Schedule, 1998 (Box 8, Folder 10)
  - ILRE 340/541 Exam Schedule, 1994-1995 (Box 8, Folder 11)
  - ILRE 340/541 Course Outline, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 12)
  - ILRE 340/541 Packet Table of Contents, 1989-1995 (Box 8, Folder 13)
  - ILRE 340/541 Library Reserve Forms, 1993-1995 (Box 8, Folder 14)
  - ILRE 340/541 Module Summary, 1992-1995 (Box 8, Folder 15)
  - ILRE 340/541 Handouts, 1994 (Box 8, Folder 16)
  - ILRE 340/541 Section (Box 8, Folder 17)
  - ILRE 340/541 Memos and Letter, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 18)
  - ILRE 340/541 Prelim 1, 1992-1997 (Box 8, Folder 19)
  - ILRE 340/541 Prelim 2, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 20)
  - ILRE 340/541 Materials For Library Reserve, 1983-1994 (Box 8, Folder 21)
  - ILRE 340/541 Final Exam, 1994-1997 (Box 8, Folder 22)
  - ILRE 340/541 Course Evaluations, 1991-1997 (Box 8, Folder 23)
  - ILRE 340/541 Grade Forms, 1987-1996 (Box 8, Folder 24)
  - ILRLE 340/541 Course Evaluation Statistics, 1997 (Box 8, Folder 25)
  - NCS Answer Sheets (Box 8, Folder 26)
- Computer disks (Box 9)
  - Computer Media (Box 9, Folder 1)
- Magnetic storage (Box 10)
  - Computer Tapes Labor 2, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 1)
  - Computer Tapes Labor 1, 1983 (Box 10, Folder 2)
  - Computer Tapes Multi, 1980 (Box 10, Folder 3)
  - Computer Tapes Patrick or Larry Kahn, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 4)
  - Computer Tapes KA1250, 1975 (Box 10, Folder 5)
  - Computer Tapes Living, 1982 (Box 10, Folder 6)
  - Computer Tapes A8586A, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 7)
  - Computer Tapes Au8182, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 8)
  - Computer Tapes Europe, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 9)
  - Computer Tapes 907395, 1985 (Box 10, Folder 10)
  - Computer Tapes LKCYB2, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 11)
  - Computer Tapes, 1991 (Box 10, Folder 12)
  - Computer Tapes, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 13)
  - Computer Tapes, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 14)
  - Computer Tapes COLLKI, 1986 (Box 10, Folder 15)
  - Computer Tapes LKCYB, 1990 (Box 10, Folder 16)
- Research files (Box 11)
  - CU-BU-PRG 5 Pairs (Box 11)
  - BU-NU-PRG 8 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 1)
  - CU-NU-PRG 5 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 2)
  - RU-NU-PRG 5 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 3)
  - RU-BU-PRG 5 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 4)
  - CU-BU-PRG 5 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 5)
  - RU-NU-PRG 5 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 6)
  - NU-BU-PRG 8 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 7)
  - RU-BU-PRG 5 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 8)
  - PRG 1-2-3-4 20 Individuals (Box 11, Folder 9)
  - IBM Fortran Coding Form (Box 11, Folder 10)
  - BU-NU-PRG 8 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 11)
  - PRG 1-2-3-4 20 Individuals (Box 11, Folder 12)
  - CU-NU-PRG 5 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 13)
  - Option Extr Forms, 1994 (Box 11, Folder 14)
  - NU-BU-PRG 8 Pairs (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - q (Box 11, Folder 15)
  - Fortran Coding Form (Box 11, Folder 16)
- Magnetic storage (Box 12)
  - Computer Tapes COLLK2, 1986 (Box 12, Folder 1)
  - Computer Tapes IR5678 (Box 12, Folder 2)
  - Computer Tapes M0P2A, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 3)
  - Computer Tapes DANNY, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 4)
  - Computer Tapes LARRY, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 5)
  - Computer Tapes BRNMOP, 1989 (Box 12, Folder 6)
  - Computer Tapes TTS237, 1976 (Box 12, Folder 7)
  - Computer Tapes CPS76A, 1985 (Box 12, Folder 8)
  - Computer Tapes, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 9)
  - Computer Tapes EUROPZ, 1990 (Box 12, Folder 10)
  - Computer Tapes ISSP88, 1991 (Box 12, Folder 11)
- Labor Economics workshops, 1998-1999 (Box 13)
  - Supplementary Sessions Live Opponents 21 total pairs (Folder 1 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 1)
  - Supplementary Sessions Live Opponents 21 total copies (Folder 2 of 2) (Box 13, Folder 2)
  - Mike Conlin August 30 1999 (Box 13, Folder 3)
  - April 19, 1999 Robert Moffitt, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 4)
  - Tom Dunn April 12, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 5)
  - LaSHAWN Richberg May 5/3/99, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 6)
  - Terry Thomason April 26, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 7)
  - Martin Gaynor March 15, 1999, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 8)
  - Lee Lillard March 8, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 9)
  - David Galenson April 5, 1999, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 10)
  - Richard Burkhauser March 29, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 11)
  - Jeon, Haekung January 25, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 12)
  - Linda Wong February 22, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 13)
  - Blau, Francine February 15, 1999 (Box 13, Folder 14)
  - Elizabeth Peters February 8, 1999, 1997-1999 (Box 13, Folder 15)
  - Abowd, John February 1, 1999, 1998-1999 (Box 13, Folder 16)
  - November 23, 1998 Nada Eissa (Box 13, Folder 17)
  - October 19, 1998 Jenny Hunt (Box 13, Folder 18)
  - October 5, 1998 Erling Barth (Box 13, Folder 19)
  - November 16, 1998 Ronald Ehrenberg (Box 13, Folder 20)
  - November 9, 1998 Shub Debgupta (Box 13, Folder 21)
  - November 2, 1998 Jesse Leary (Box 13, Folder 22)
  - October 26, 1998 Ken Chay - Berkley + Princeton (Box 13, Folder 23)
  - September 29, 1998 Alan Krueger (Box 13, Folder 24)
  - Bishop, John "Is Welfare Reform Succeeding?", 1998 (Box 13, Folder 25)
  - September 14, 1998 Rob Olsen (Box 13, Folder 26)
  - August 31, 1998 L. Kahn (Box 13, Folder 27)
  - April 27, 1998 Dean Lillard (Box 13, Folder 28)
- Labor Economics workshops, 1998-1999 (Box 14)
  - April 8, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 1)
  - April 1, 1998 Mark An, 1997-1998 (Box 14, Folder 2)
  - March 25, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 3)
  - March 9, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 4)
  - March 2, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 5)
  - February 23, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 6)
  - February 2, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 7)
  - February 6, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 8)
  - Samid Hussain December 6, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 9)
  - Richard Chaykowski November 29, 1999, 1999-2000 (Box 14, Folder 10)
  - Edward Lazear November 12, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 11)
  - Ann Horvath-Rose November 8, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 12)
  - Deborah Anderson November 15, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 13)
  - Andre Souza November 1, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 14)
  - John Abowd October 25, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 15)
  - John Abowd Oct. 18, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 16)
  - Jeff Smith October 14, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 17)
  - Andre de-Souza November 1, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 18)
  - Gordon Dahl October 4, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 19)
  - LE Workshop Fall '99, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 20)
  - LE Workshop Spring 1999 (Box 14, Folder 21)
  - LE Workshop Fall '98 Schedule, 1996-1998 (Box 14, Folder 22)
  - LE Workshop Fall '98 Misc. Correspondence, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 23)
  - LE Workshop Fall '98, 1998 (Box 14, Folder 24)
  - Labor Economics Workshop Spring 1998 (Box 14, Folder 25)
  - Orley Ashenfelter September 27, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 26)
  - Dan Black September 13, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 27)
  - Brewer Dominic, 1999 (Box 14, Folder 28)
- Student financial aid and visa files, LE reserve readings (Box 15)
  - Docs. Relating to Women in the Economy, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 1)
  - Explaining Trends in the Gender Wage Gap, 1998 (Box 15, Folder 2)
  - Rising Wage Inequality and the Gender Gap, 1994 (Box 15, Folder 3)
  - "Seneca Falls: The Enduring Sentiments", 1998 (Box 15, Folder 4)
  - "Court Spells Out Rules For Finding Sex Harassment", 1998 (Box 15, Folder 5)
  - "For Marriage Tax, a Messy Divorce", 1998 (Box 15, Folder 6)
  - "Effect of Child Care Costs on Married Women's Labor Force Participation", 1992 (Box 15, Folder 7)
  - Singe Mothers and Their Children Ch. 3, 1986 (Box 15, Folder 8)
  - Small Change Ch. 2- "Aggregate Differentials", 1993 (Box 15, Folder 9)
  - Women's Work and Women's Lives Ch. 10- "Central in the Family", 1992 (Box 15, Folder 10)
  - Women's Work and Women's Lives Ch.6 - "Women and Work in Communist", 1992 (Box 15, Folder 11)
  - Women's Work and Women's Lives Ch.7- "Interaction of Women's Work", 1992 (Box 15, Folder 12)
  - Rosenblum, David, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 13)
  - Liu, Albert, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 14)
  - Stixrud, Jora, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 15)
  - Wilde, Elizabeth, 2002 (Box 15, Folder 16)
  - Bowen, Tonja, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 17)
  - Busso. Matias, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 18)
  - Cong, Chao, 2002-2003 (Box 15, Folder 19)
  - Crespo, Anna, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 20)
  - Hernani-Limarino, Werner, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 21)
  - Shi, Xinzheng, 2000-2003 (Box 15, Folder 22)
  - Gittings, Kaj, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 23)
  - At Home and Abroad US Labor Market Performance in Internat. Perspective (Box 15, Folder 24)
  - At Home and Abroad US Labor Market Performance in Internat. Perspective (Box 15, Folder 25)
  - Boyer LE 140 Scanned (Box 15, Folder 26)
  - To Do Boyer 140 (Box 15, Folder 27)
  - Docs. Relating to Labor Economics, 2003-2004 (Box 15, Folder 28)
  - Discrimination: Empirical Evidence from the United States, 1987 (Box 15, Folder 29)
  - Docs. Relating to Web Design + HTML, 2001-2003 (Box 15, Folder 30)
  - Economics Fall/Winter 2002 (Box 15, Folder 31)
  - Using Procite to Enter Information on Books and Articles (Box 15, Folder 32)
  - Lee, Youngro, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 33)
  - Price, Joseph, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 34)
  - Docs. Relating to Robert Hutchens, 2003 (Box 15, Folder 35)
  - CourseInfo 4.0 Tutorial Building a Course Web Site, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 36)
  - Journal of Economic Perspectives, 1992 (Box 15, Folder 37)
  - Journal of Economic Perspectives "Universal Health Insurance in the Clinton Plan", 1994 (Box 15, Folder 38)
  - "Clinton Proposes Aid for Disabled Returning to Jobs", 1998 (Box 15, Folder 39)
  - Economic Security Welfare Module Lecture 2 Temporary Assistance for Needy Families, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 40)
  - Economic Security ILRLE 340 Welfare Module Lecture 1- Introducing Poverty, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 41)
  - Earned Income Tax Credit Notes, 1999 (Box 15, Folder 42)
  - Economic Security ILRLE 340 Welfare Module - Lecture 1 Introducing Poverty, 2001 (Box 15, Folder 43)